Louise Z. Young Photographs MS156
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Negatives and Prints, 1947 -- 1970; MS156.001; 1.0 Linear Feet; 498 Digital Object(s)
  - Plaques - Anderson Hall, 1951 -- 1961; MS156.001.001.00056 (Box 1)
    - Anderson Hall Plaque for Arthur J. Anderson with names of contributors, 1961-07-11; MS156.001.001.00056.00015; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Anderson Hall --Plaques --Anderson, Arthur J.; negatives (photographic)
    - Anderson Hall Plaque for Arthur J. Anderson, Obrion, Russell, 1961-07-11; MS156.001.001.00056.00016; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Anderson Hall --Plaques --Anderson, Arthur J. --Obrion, Russell; negatives (photographic)
  - Construction at Dewyck, 1951 -- 1961; MS156.001.001.00057 (Box 1)
    - Construction at Dewick Dining Hall on "Latin Way", 1961-07-12; MS156.001.001.00057.00001; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Dewick Dining Hall --Construction --Latin Way; negatives (photographic)
    - Construction at Dewick Dining Hall, 1961-07-12; MS156.001.001.00057.00002; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Dewick Dining Hall --Construction; negatives (photographic)
  - Murals - Alumni Lounge, 1961; MS156.001.001.00058 (Box 1)
    - Mural of group of men and women from Alumnae Lounge, 1961-09-15; MS156.001.001.00058.00001; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Mural of boat scene from Alumnae Lounge, 1961-09-15; MS156.001.001.00058.00002; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Mural of building on hill (behind couches) from Alumnae Lounge, 1961-09-15; MS156.001.001.00058.00003; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Mural of Alumni (behind couches) from Alumnae Lounge, 1961-09-15; MS156.001.001.00058.00004; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Mural of men and woman from Alumnae Lounge, 1961-09-15; MS156.001.001.00058.00005; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Mural of men (V12?) from Alumnae Lounge, 1961-09-15; MS156.001.001.00058.00006; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Mural of women from Alumnae Lounge, 1961-09-15; MS156.001.001.00058.00007; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Mural of men from Alumnae Lounge, 1961-09-15; MS156.001.001.00058.00008; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
  - Architectural Exteriors, 1961; MS156.001.001.00059 (Box 1)
    - Women walking down sidewalk beside fence, (Arch. Exteriors for TAR), 1961-10-25; MS156.001.001.00059.00001; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Students --Arch. Exteriors for TAR; negatives (photographic)
    - Students waiting outside building, 1961-10-25; MS156.001.001.00059.00002; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Students outside Braker, 1961-10-25; MS156.001.001.00059.00003; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Students --Braker Hall --Arch. Exteriors for TAR; negatives (photographic)
  - Fletcher Library, 1961; MS156.001.001.00060 (Box 1)
    - Students studying in Fletcher Library, 1961-11-09; MS156.001.001.00060.00001; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Fletcher Library; negatives (photographic)
    - Students on Fletcher Row, 1961-11-09; MS156.001.001.00060.00002; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Fletcher Row; negatives (photographic)
  - Fletcher library and fletcher row, 1961; MS156.001.001.00061 (Box 1)
    Pictures taken two nights after the "big snow"
    - Students in front of Statton Hall at night, 1961-12-14; MS156.001.001.00061.00001; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Linda Rosen and Bert Meltzer
      Night Scene --Stratton Hall --Students --Snow; negatives (photographic)
    - Students' silhouettes on snow at night, 1961-12-14; MS156.001.001.00061.00002; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Fran Spencer and Michael Frisch
      Night Scene --Students --Snow; negatives (photographic)
  - Memorial steps, 1962; MS156.001.001.00062 (Box 1)
    - Memorial Steps from across road, 1962-04-19; MS156.001.001.00062.00001; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Memorial Steps; negatives (photographic)
    - Memorial Steps, 1962-04-19; MS156.001.001.00062.00002; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
  - Campus scenes, 1962; MS156.001.001.00063 (Box 1)
    - People sitting by Alumni Gate (?), 1962-04-26; MS156.001.001.00063.00001; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Campus Scenes --Alumni Gate(?); negatives (photographic)
    - People sitting on grass in quad (?), 1962-04-26; MS156.001.001.00063.00002; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Campus Scenes --Quad; negatives (photographic)
    - Pair walking by Eaton Memorial Library, 1962-04-26; MS156.001.001.00063.00003; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Campus Scenes --Eaton Memorial Library --Goddard Chapel; negatives (photographic)
    - Boy and girl talking by lamp pole, 1962-04-26; MS156.001.001.00063.00004; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Campus Scenes --Students; negatives (photographic)
    - Telephone operator in Ballou Hall, 1962-04-26; MS156.001.001.00063.00005; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Ballou Hall --Telephone operator; negatives (photographic)
  - New buildings tufts campus, 1962; MS156.001.001.00064 (Box 1)
    - Houston Hall construction, 1962-07-12; MS156.001.001.00064.00001; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Buildings --Houston Hall --Construction; negatives (photographic)
    - Fletcher construction, 1962-07-12; MS156.001.001.00064.00002; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Buildings --Fletcher School --Construction; negatives (photographic)
    - Tilton Hall construction, 1962-07-12; MS156.001.001.00064.00003; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Buildings --Tilton Hall --Construction; negatives (photographic)
    - Eliot-Pearson Hall construction, 1962-07-12; MS156.001.001.00064.00004; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Buildings --Eliot-Pearson Hall -- Construction; negatives (photographic)
    - Lincoln-Filene Hall construction, 1962-07-12; MS156.001.001.00064.00005; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Buildings --Lincoln-Filene Hall --Construction; negatives (photographic)
  - Alumni house under snow, 1963; MS156.001.001.00065 (Box 1)
    - Left angle view of Alumni House under snow, 1963-03-03; MS156.001.001.00065.00001; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Alumni House --Snow; negatives (photographic)
    - Right angle view of Alumni House and driveway under snow, 1963-03-03; MS156.001.001.00065.00002; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Front view of Alumni House under snow, 1963-03-03; MS156.001.001.00065.00003; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
  - Commencement Tufts, 1963; MS156.001.001.00066 (Box 1)
    - Group of honorary degree recipients at Commencement, 1963-06-09; MS156.001.001.00066.00001; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - William H. Curtis and Francis Keppel receiving hood and honorary degree at Commencement, 1963-06-09; MS156.001.001.00066.00002; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement --Honorary degrees --Curtis, William H. --Keppel, Francis; negatives (photographic)
    - Lyndon B. Johnson receiving hood and honorary degree at Commencement, 1963-06-09; MS156.001.001.00066.00003; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement --Honorary degrees --Johnson, Lyndon B.; negatives (photographic)
    - Walter B. Wriston receiving hood and honorary degree at Commencement, 1963-06-09; MS156.001.001.00066.00004; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement --Honorary degrees --Wriston, Walter B.; negatives (photographic)
    - Andrew N. Wyeth receiving hood and honorary degree at Commencement, 1963-06-09; MS156.001.001.00066.00005; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement --Honorary degrees --Wyeth, Andrew N.; negatives (photographic)
    - Mason E. Bennett receiving hood and honorary degree at Commencement, 1963-06-09; MS156.001.001.00066.00006; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement --Honorary degrees --Bennett, Mason E.; negatives (photographic)
    - Paul C. Reardon and Cameron S. Thompson receiving hood and honorary degree at Commencement, 1963-06-09; MS156.001.001.00066.00007; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement --Honorary degrees --Reardon, Paul C. --Thompson, Cameron S.; negatives (photographic)
    - Joseph A. McCarthy and Mason E. Bennett receiving hood and honorary degree at Commencement, 1963-06-09; MS156.001.001.00066.00008; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement --Honorary degrees --McCarthy, Joseph A. --Bennett, Mason, E.; negatives (photographic)
    - Thomas H. Kuchel and Henry A. Peck receiving hood and honorary degree at Commencement, 1963-06-09; MS156.001.001.00066.00009; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement --Honorary degrees --Kuchel, Thomas H --Peck, Henry A.; negatives (photographic)
    - George J. W. Pennington and David Rapport receiving hood and honorary degree at Commencement, 1963-06-09; MS156.001.001.00066.00010; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement --Honorary degrees --Pennington, George J. W. --Rapport, David; negatives (photographic)
    - Thomas H. Kuchel receiving hood and honorary degree at Commencement, 1963-06-09; MS156.001.001.00066.00011; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement --Honorary degrees --Kuchel, Thomas H.; negatives (photographic)
    - Lyndon B. Johnson speaking at Commencement, 1963-06-09; MS156.001.001.00066.00012; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement --Speaker --Johnson, Lyndon B.; negatives (photographic)
    - Marshals at Commencement, 1963-06-09; MS156.001.001.00066.00013; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement --Marshals; negatives (photographic)
    - Lyndon B. Johnson, Thomas H. Kuchel, Nils Yngve Wessell, and Francis Keppel at Commencement, 1963-06-09; MS156.001.001.00066.00014; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement --Johnson, Lyndon B. --Kuchel, Thomas H. --Wessell, Nils Yngve --Keppel, Francis; negatives (photographic)
    - Lyndon B. Johnson with Joan Fitzgerald, 1963-06-09; MS156.001.001.00066.00015; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Commencement --Johnson, Lyndon B. --Fitzgerald, Joan; negatives (photographic)
  - New library site, 1964; MS156.001.001.00067 (Box 1)
    - New Wessell Library site with crane, 1964-02-12; MS156.001.001.00067.00001; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Wessell Library --Construction; negatives (photographic)
    - New Wessell Library site with truck, 1964-02-12; MS156.001.001.00067.00002; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - New Wessell Library site with cars, 1964-02-12; MS156.001.001.00067.00003; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
  - Tufts exteriors, 1964; MS156.001.001.00068 (Box 1)
    - New chemistry wing, the Michael Building, 1964-10-01; MS156.001.001.00068.00001; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Buildings --The Michael Building (?); negatives (photographic)
    - Curtis Hall in white, 1964-10-01; MS156.001.001.00068.00002; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Buildings --Curtis Hall; negatives (photographic)
    - Barnum wing construction, 1964-10-01; MS156.001.001.00068.00003; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Buildings --Barnum wing --Construction; negatives (photographic)
    - The Michael Building viewed from Bush Hall, 1964-10-01; MS156.001.001.00068.00004; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Buildings --The Michael Building (?) --Bush Hall; negatives (photographic)
    - Exterior view of Bush Hall, 1964-10-01; MS156.001.001.00068.00005; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Exterior views --Bush Hall; negatives (photographic)
    - Exterior view of Metcalf East and West, 1964-10-01; MS156.001.001.00068.00006; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Exterior view of Hodgdon Hall entrance, 1964-10-01; MS156.001.001.00068.00007; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Exterior view of Richardson House, 1964-10-01; MS156.001.001.00068.00008; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Exterior views --Richardson House; negatives (photographic)
    - Exterior view of Stratton Hall, 1964-10-01; MS156.001.001.00068.00009; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Exterior views --Stratton Hall; negatives (photographic)
    - Exterior view of Capen Hall, 1964-10-01; MS156.001.001.00068.00010; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Exterior views --Capen Hall; negatives (photographic)
    - Exterior view of Tilton Hall, 1964-10-01; MS156.001.001.00068.00011; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Exterior views --Tilton Hall; negatives (photographic)
  - Fletcher new building, 1965; MS156.001.001.00069 (Box 1)
    - View of Fletcher from tennis courts, 1965-03-10; MS156.001.001.00069.00001; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Exterior views --Fletcher School; negatives (photographic)
    - View of Fletcher from President's house, 1965-03-10; MS156.001.001.00069.00002; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
  - Exterior Miner and Curtis halls, 1965; MS156.001.001.00070 (Box 1)
    - View of Miner Hall and Curtis Hall from Anderson Hall, 1965-04-03; MS156.001.001.00070.00001; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Exterior views --Miner Hall --Curtis Hall --Anderson Hall; negatives (photographic)
    - View of Miner Hall and Curtis Hall through archway, 1965-04-03; MS156.001.001.00070.00002; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Exterior views --Miner Hall --Curtis Hall --Archway; negatives (photographic)
  - Bust of Barnum, 1967; MS156.001.001.00071 (Box 1)
    - Bust of Barnum in Barnum Lounge, 1967-10-17; MS156.001.001.00071.00001; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Barnum Lounge --Barnum, P.T. --Bust; negatives (photographic)
    - Closeup of Bust of Barnum in Barnum Lounge, 1967-10-17; MS156.001.001.00071.00002; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
  - Jumbo, 1967 -- 1970; MS156.001.001.00072 (Box 1)
    - Jumbo at Coney Island (from print series), 1967; MS156.001.001.00072.00001; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      negatives (photographic)
    - Jumbo in chains (from print series), 1968; MS156.001.001.00072.00002; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Barnum's Great Show (from print series), 1969; MS156.001.001.00072.00003; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Barnum, P.T.; negatives (photographic)
    - Group of people surrounding Jumbo, 1970; MS156.001.001.00072.00004; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Jumbo Must Go from Willimantic Thread (from print series), 1970; MS156.001.001.00072.00005; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - P.T. Barnum, 1970; MS156.001.001.00072.00006; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Jumbo March with children riding on back (from print series), 1970; MS156.001.001.00072.00007; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Big Jumbo, Little Jumbo and bust of Barnum in Barnum Lounge, 1970; MS156.001.001.00072.00008; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Jumbo --Barnum Lounge --Barnum, P.T. --Bust; negatives (photographic)
    - Jumbo in Barnum Lounge, 1970; MS156.001.001.00072.00009; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Jumbo --Barnum Lounge; negatives (photographic)
    - Cartoon of P.T. Barnum, 1970; MS156.001.001.00072.00010; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Welcome Barnum to England flags, 1970; MS156.001.001.00072.00011; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Barnum coin (1 of 2), 1970; MS156.001.001.00072.00012; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Barnum coin (2 of 2), 1970; MS156.001.001.00072.00013; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - P.T. Barnum in hat, 1970; MS156.001.001.00072.00014; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Directions to preserve carcass of "sea serpent," giant squid, seal, white whale or other marine animal, page 1, 1970; MS156.001.001.00072.00015; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Directions --Barnum, P.T.; negatives (photographic)
    - Directions to preserve carcass of "sea serpent," giant squid, seal, white whale or other marine animal, page 2, 1970; MS156.001.001.00072.00016; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Post office stamps on Barnum's envelope, 1970; MS156.001.001.00072.00017; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Postage on lett to P.T. Barnum, 1970; MS156.001.001.00072.00018; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Barnum: Man of the World magazine cover, 1970; MS156.001.001.00072.00019; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Barnum, P.T. --Magazine; negatives (photographic)
    - Barnum welcoming banquet committee list with photo of Barnum, 1970; MS156.001.001.00072.00020; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - P.T. Barnum 1874, 1970; MS156.001.001.00072.00021; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Students putting coins in Jumbo's trunk, 1970; MS156.001.001.00072.00022; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Jumbo --Barnum Lounge --Students --Traditions; negatives (photographic)
    - Students around Jumbo, 1970; MS156.001.001.00072.00023; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Jumbo --Barnum Lounge --Students; negatives (photographic)
    - Children looking up at Jumbo, 1970; MS156.001.001.00072.00024; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Jumbo --Barnum Lounge --Children; negatives (photographic)
    - Two students and Jumbo in Barnum Lounge, 1970; MS156.001.001.00072.00025; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Overhead shot of children looking at Jumbo, 1970; MS156.001.001.00072.00026; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Man cleaning bust of Barnum, 1970; MS156.001.001.00072.00027; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Man cleaning Jumbo's foot, 1970; MS156.001.001.00072.00028; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - Girls playing around Jumbo's legs, 1970; MS156.001.001.00072.00029; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - People watching cleaning of Jumbo, 1970; MS156.001.001.00072.00030; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - "To P.T. Barnum from his old friend" written on back of photograph (?), 1970; MS156.001.001.00072.00031; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
    - M'lle Jenny Lind performance program, 1970; MS156.001.001.00072.00032; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Ling, M'lle Jenny --Program; negatives (photographic)
    - "J is for Jumbo" child's book page, 1970; MS156.001.001.00072.00033; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Jumbo --Book; negatives (photographic)
    - Jumbo in cage (from print series), 1970; MS156.001.001.00072.00034; Duette Photographers (Box 1)
      Jumbo --Print series; negatives (photographic)
  - Prints of Jumbo, commencement, and buildings circa 1950-1961, MS156.001.002.00001; Duette Photographers (Box Shared 136)